mindjourneyshypnosis.com 2018-07-10

# Privacy Policy – Mind Journeys Hypnosis

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, MindJourneysHypnosis.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting MindJourneysHypnosis.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Mailing Policy  
**When you request information from or membership in the MindJourneysHypnosis.com website, as an integral part of your membership, we add your name and email address to our mailing list so that we may tell you about new articles, classes, recordings and other material as soon as they are posted.

In order to maintain the highest level of security and privacy, our mailing list is professionally managed for us by [SendPulse](http://www.sendpulse.com/ "SendPulse Mailing List Management"), one of the top list management companies on the Internet.

As part of your membership, we may, from time to time, send you information about our services, promotions, newsletters, or new offers, using your email address and any other information you give us, so that we may provide you with information or other services, until you ask us to stop. (You can freely use the ‘unsubscribe’ instructions and unsubscribe link included in each email from us.)

When you request information or other services from us, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services that you requested, until you ask us to stop. (You can freely use the ‘unsubscribe’ instructions and unsubscribe link included in each email from us, or until the information or service is no longer available.)

We will never use your email address or other information to send you any unsolicited messages or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party to use in spamming you.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference.  If you purchase a product through such links, we may be paid a commission. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of MindJourneysHypnosis.com then you may email us via our contact page ( <http://mindjourneyshypnosis.com/contact-me/> ).
